请求支援 红色警报 发生交火
Dispatch! Signal red! Shots fired!
发生交火
Shots fired!
多名嫌疑人 把所有人都派来
Multiple suspects! Send everybody!
嘿 你中枪了吗
Hey, you shot?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想我没事
I don't think so.
刚刚到底发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
NCIS 新奥尔良
S03E21
我的电脑呢
What about my computer?
那个 网络摄像头还是什么的
The... the webcam or whatever it's called.
我是说 他们能不能黑进去
I mean, c-can't they hack into that
在我不知情的情况下偷拍我
and record me without my knowing?
我们已经采取了防入侵措施 市长先生
We've already disabled it, Mr. Mayor.
你的笔记本电脑和手机也是
Same with your laptop and cell.
你们确定没问题了吗 因为
Yeah. You sure about that? 'Cause, uh,
我不想再有什么漏洞 我的麻烦已经够多了
I don't need no more leaks. I got enough problems.
要知道 有些人不遗余力地
Certain people try to bring me down
想扳倒我
any way they can, you know?
我们接下来会检查您的车子和家里
We'll scan your car and home next.
目前为止 这个房间是安全的
But, for now, this room's secure.
好的 电话也安全吗
Good. Phones, too?
呃 别用座机
Uh, don't use landlines.
但如果你的助理发现 听筒里有回音或敲击声
But make sure your assistant lets you know
让她一定要告诉你
if she hears any echoes or clicks.
有可能是线路窃听
Could mean a wiretap.
如果真的是窃听 我们应该可以追查到源头
And, if so, we should be able to trace its source.
手机呢 没问题吗
What about cell phones-- they good?
手机没问题
Cell's good.
好的 那我们也没问题了
All right. We're good, then.
两千 是吗
2,000, right?
不必了 我们会给你寄账单
Uh, that's okay, we'll just bill you.
不 不行
Uh, no. No, no.
不要账单
No bills.
这事只有你我知道 明白吗
It's between us, you understand?
明白了
Understood.
好的
Okay.
-你好 -Frank 我是Hamilton
- Hello? - Frank, it's Hamilton.
你确定这条线没问题吗
Are you sure this line is secure?
说实话 我现在对什么都不确定了
Honestly, I'm not sure about anything anymore.
让我非常困扰
Gotten in pretty deep here.
你也不该感到确定 市长先生 因为我
Nor should you be, Mr. Mayor, 'cause I'm gonna be
就站在你跟前 宝贝儿
up and in your grill, baby.
他都清理过手机了 我们怎么还能窃听他
How can we still hear him if they swept his cell?
你是无法清理3P的影子应用的
You can't sweep a Triple P shadow app,
这个应用让我能窃听并录下
which allows me to listen to and record
听得见的任何声音
any and everything within earshot.
问题在于 不是所有事情
Problem is, anything and everything isn't covered
都在窃听令的许可范围
under the wiretap warrant.
只能是关于清水市
Only what's related to Clearwater
或者他所谓的海外行贿基金
or his alleged offshore slush funds.
还有Javier Garcia的谋杀案
And Javier Garcia's murder.
告诉Jess
Let Jess know,
我这段时间不能见她了
uh, I won't be seeing her for a while.
不能冒险让媒体再挖出什么绯闻了
Can't risk the media finding out about any more of these affairs.
-停止录音 -等等 什么
- Stop recording. - Wait, what?
私人信息
Personal information is not covered
不在窃听范围之内
under the scope of the wiretap.
听着 Dwayne 如果不能严格按照要求执行
Look, Dwayne, if this isn't done within the strict parameters
在法庭上是站不住脚的
of the order, it won't stand up in court.
市长并不干净 Karen
Mayor's dirty, Karen.
Rita让这个案子正式成立了
Look, Rita's put together a solid circumstantial case,
但是Jenkins... 他是唯一一个愿意
but Jenkins-- he was the only judge willing to risk
冒险跟Hamilton对立 同意窃听的法官
going up against Hamilton to grant the tap.
我知道你们有多想扳倒他
I know how bad you want to take him down,
但如果你们不按法律条文办事
but if you don't do this by the book,
你们会失去窃听许可
you're gonna blow the wiretap.
Hamilton就会从谋杀案脱身
And Hamilton gets away with murder.
还有其它案件
And everything else.
停止录音
Stop recording.
好了 我有案子了
Ah, all right, I got a case.
继续监视市长
Keep monitoring the mayor.
你确定Patton知道监听的关键字吗
Are you sure Patton knows what keywords to listen for?
他知道清水市案子的
Is he read in on Clearwater,
全部细节了吗
every detail?
不 不是全部
No, not everything.
那我要是你 我会待在这里
Then I'd stay put if I were you.
拿下Hamilton可能只有这一次机会
May only get this one shot at Hamilton.
Pride还好吗 他听起来怎么样
Yeah, is Pride all right? How'd he sound?
纠结
Torn.
必须说服他待在那里
Had to talk him into staying put,
集中精力扳倒Hamilton
focusing on trying to get Hamilton
在他干掉我们之前
before Hamilton gets us.
是啊 King对工作很忠诚
Yeah, King's loyal to the job.
让他放弃主导案件侦破很不容易
It's not easy for him not taking the lead on a case.
所以我们更要把这个案子办得漂漂亮亮
All the more reason for us to kick ass on this one.
你要我去接Percy吗
Do you want me to go pick up Percy?
不用 我已经在咖啡店这里了
No, I'm already here at the coffee shop.
我们一会儿在犯罪...
We'll meet you at the crime...
现场见
...scene.
Lasalle
Lasalle?
Lasalle 你还在吗
Lasalle, you still there?
是 我还在
Yeah, I'm still here.
一会见
We'll see you in a bit.
嗨
Hey!
乡下鼠
Country Mouse.
早知道是你来接我
If I knew you were my ride,
我会给你带个羊角面包
I would've picked you up a croissant.
一切还好吗
Everything all right?
当然 我们出发吧
Yeah, sure. Let's roll.
嘿 你确定没什么心事吗
Hey, you sure nothing's bothering you?
我吗 没啊 怎么了
Me? No, why?
我不知道 也许是因为这一路上
I don't know, maybe 'cause you only said, like,
你只跟我说了两个字
two words to me on the way over.
是我哎 怎么回事
Come on, it's me. What?
Gregorio 我们掌握了什么
Gregorio, what do we got?
你也好啊 Christopher
Hello to you, too, Christopher.
哦 姐们儿 他心情不太好
Oh, girl, he is in a mood.
看得出来
I can see that.
抢劫团伙很专业
Heist crew were pros,
干掉了监控 阻断了通讯
took out cameras, jammed communication,
很清楚地知道他们想要的东西是什么 在哪里
knew exactly what they were after and where to get it.
Sebastian 货物是什么
Sebastian, what's the haul?
运往Fort Bragg基地的几百个MP5冲锋枪
Couple hundred MP5s headed to Fort Bragg.
海军还在清查库存
The Navy's still doing an inventory
以获知准确数目 不过...
to get an exact count, but...
那可是大批量的重火力武器
That's a lot of serious firepower.
我是说 这不可能只是为了
I mean, this can't just be about selling them
到黑市上去卖吧
on the black market.
我们遇到了民兵组织之类的吗
We're dealing with some kind of militia?
不管他们是谁 都是有备而来的
Well, whoever it was, they came prepared.
根据铁路警察的说法 他们都有防弹衣
According to the railway cops, they all had body armor,
用的是AR-15突击步枪 震荡手雷
were using AR-15s, concussive grenades.
有多少人受伤
How many were injured?
怪就怪在这儿 没人受伤
That's the thing-- none.
哇 抢劫团伙用了AR-15突击步枪 手雷
Whoa. Heist crew using AR-15s, grenades,
带着MP5冲锋枪逃跑 竟然没一个警察中枪
making off with MP5s, and no cop gets shot?
不 警察们被射击了 但射中他们的不是子弹
Oh, no, cops were shot all right, just not with bullets.
没错 不是致命的子弹
Yeah, not with lethal rounds.
而是橡胶子弹
With rubber bullets.
专门设计的复合材料
Specifically designed composite,
就像中了一记重拳一样
packs a heck of a punch,
尤其是用AR-15射出来
especially coming out of an AR-15.
能打得你喘不过气来
It's more than enough to knock the wind out of you.
-但不会死人 -那么问题来了
- But not kill. - Which begs the question,
什么样的抢劫团伙 去偷上百个致命武器
what kind of heist crew steals hundreds of lethal weapons
会带非致命武器呢
using nonlethal rounds?
是啊 这说不通
Yeah. Doesn't make sense.
是的 但幸亏铁路警察
Yeah, well, fortunately the rail cops
用的是真子弹
were using live ammo.
他们打中了一个团伙成员
They tagged one of the crew.
流了不少血 我应该能通过DNA查明身份
Lost a lot of blood. I should be able to get a DNA I.D.
好的 有发现就告诉我们 Sebastian
All right, let us know what you find, Sebastian.
那个有钱人是谁
Who's the fat cat?
枪支制造公司的老板
Owner of the company that makes the guns,
Justus Bancroft
Justus Bancroft.
或者说是受害者
Or the victim.
慢着 在ATF里待了那么多年
Whoa. Spent a lot of years at ATF
烟酒、火器与爆炸物管理局
看过Bancroft的枪械产品所造成的伤害
seeing the pain Bancroft guns cause.
很难把他们当成受害人
Hardly makes them a victim.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
海军罪案调查处 可以和我聊聊吗
NCIS. Mind if I get a word?
不好意思 请问有什么问题吗
Sorry, is there a problem?
不 当然没问题
No, no, no, not at all.
只是 呃
It's just that, uh, well,
我们已经把知道的都告诉警察了
we already told the police everything we know.
而且我们必须走了
And we have to go.
抱歉 请问你是
I'm sorry, who are you?
Nadine
Nadine.
Bancroft
Bancroft.
特别探员Lasalle
Special Agent Lasalle.
我们之后会和警方沟通 但如果你不介意的话...
We'll talk with NOPD afterwards, but if you don't mind...
当然不介意 尽管问
No, no, of course, of course. Ask me anything.
只不过 呃 我们明天
Well, it's just that, uh, we're hosting
要举办年度慈善活动
our annual charity event tomorrow.
我倒是觉得几百支冲锋枪不知所踪
I kind of think a couple hundred missing submachine guns
比你们的小派对更重要 不是吗
trumps your little party, don't you?
Percy
Percy.
无意冒犯 但是
No disrespect, but, uh,
我们的工作还是要做的 而且枪支数量很多
we got to do our jobs, and that's a lot of guns.
对 相信我 我理解
Oh, yeah, trust me, I know.
这也不是我们第一次遭遇这种事了
It's not the first time we've been hit, either.
你们以前也被抢劫过
You've been robbed before?
没有这么严重 但是有过
Well, not to this extent, but yes.
FBI ATF 他们都
Uh, the FBI, ATF, they both investigated
调查过前两次抢劫 但无功而返
the other two times, and, uh, come up empty.
我很高兴没有警察受伤
I'm just glad none of the police got hurt.
三次 这里面一定有什么联系
Well, third time, there's got to be a connection.
我们会深入调查 并通知你我们的进展
We'll dig into it and let you know what we find.
-好的 -我们会和你保持联系
- All right. - We'll be in touch.
你随时可以联系我
You, uh, call me anytime.
-谢谢 -好了
- Thank you. - All right.
谢谢
Thanks.
我觉得King
I don't think King
不会喜欢你对她说话的态度
would've much liked the way you talked to her.
我还不喜欢你对我说话的态度呢
Don't much like the way you talked to me.
她的反应就好像这一切
She acted like this was nothing more
只是些麻烦而已
than an inconvenience.
你不觉得奇怪吗
That didn't bother you?
哦 我忘了
Oh, I forgot,
你对什么都无所谓
nothing's bothering you.
对吧
Right.
在我的办公桌上工作还自在吗
Making yourself at home at my desk?
哦 Pride 不 不 抱歉
Oh, Pride, no, no, no. I'm sorry.
我就是 我不想
I just, I didn't want to
-打扰你和Patton -没事 Sebastian
- bother you and Patton. - It's okay, Sebastian.
开个玩笑 坐吧
Just teasing. Sit down.
能和你换位置再高兴不过了 真的
Be more than happy to trade places with you, believe me.
坐在窃听设备旁有点儿无聊吧
Sitting on a wiretap's kind of boring, huh?
不如说是单调乏味
More like tedious.
而且 我知道了越来越多
Plus, I'm learning more about Hamilton
压根不想知道的Hamilton的事 太多了
than I ever wanted to know. A lot more.
但没能把他和谋杀案或清水市联系起来吗
But nothing that connects him to the murders or Clearwater?
还没有
Not yet.
但这只是
But it's just
时间问题
a matter of time.
案子进展怎么样了
Where are you on the case?
用我在犯罪现场找到的DNA
Well, using the DNA I found at the crime scene,
我尝试确认伤者的身份
I'm trying to I.D. our wounded bad guy,
但迄今为止 一无所获
but nothing's coming up so far,
这个 有点儿奇怪
which is, you know, a little odd.
好的 但并非异常
Okay. But not unusual.
我刚和FBI打完电话
I just got off the phone with FBI,
看了之前的抢劫记录 他们也没有任何发现
checked on the prior heists, and they got nothing, either.
难以置信
Well, that's hard to believe.
三起抢劫大案 没有一点证据
Three high-profile hits, no evidence.
这怎么可能呢
How's that possible?
更奇怪的是 以前被偷的枪
Even stranger, none of the past stolen guns
没有一支出现在街头或者黑市
have showed up on the street or black market.
它们就像消失了一样
It's as if they just disappeared.
也许我该和你们一起调查的
Yeah, maybe I should get involved.
不行 Hamilton知道你在查他
No, Hamilton knows you're after him.
你现在不能松懈 这太重要了
You can't let up now. It's too important.
几百支失踪的枪也很重要
So is a couple hundred missing guns.
哦 怪不得我一直匹配不上
Oh, no wonder I didn't get a match.
我把查找的罪犯性别设置成了男性 而不是女性
I programmed the I.D. search for bad guys, not bad girls.
这是性别歧视 顺便说一下
That's male bias, by the way.
我为此道歉
I apologize for that.
Josephine Bellacroix
Uh, Josephine Bellacroix.
中尉 新奥尔良出生
First Lieutenant, born in New Orleans.
海军陆战队员吗
A Marine?
对 而且档案非常干净
Yeah, flawless record, too.
她去过索马里和苏丹
She did a tour in Somalia and Sudan.
一年前离开了军队
Left the Corps a year ago.
刚好在第一次劫案发生前
Just before the first heist.
不知道是什么让她开始偷枪的
Wonder what made her start stealing guns.
带她回来 查清楚
Pick her up, find out.
-在你去之前... -好的 我先给Lasalle打电话
- And before you do that... - All right, I'll call Lasalle.
他和Sonja还在值外勤
He and Sonja are still in the field.
Sebastian 着手调查她的同事
Sebastian, start looking for known associates,
看能不能找到她的同伙
see if we can find out who she's working with.
这就查
I'm on it.
嘿
Hey.
我们可以的 不要担心
We got this. Don't worry about us.
如果你一直对我采取沉默的方式
If you're gonna keep giving me the silent treatment
来折磨我
and being mean to me...
我没折磨你
I'm not being mean to you.
好吧 那是怎么回事
Okay, so what's your problem?
我不明白
I don't understand.
我就是对今早的事情很吃惊
I was just surprised this morning,
看到你和那个人在咖啡馆
seeing you with that guy at the coffee shop.
等等 Tom吗
Wait, Tom?
我不知道你在跟人约会
I didn't know you were dating anybody.
我没在约会
I'm not dating anybody.
只是喝咖啡而已
It was just coffee.
再说 我一点都不了解他
Besides, I barely know that guy.
你已经了解到可以亲他了
Well, you knew him well enough to kiss him.
我没亲他 是他亲的我
I didn't kiss-- he kissed me.
你是在吃醋吗
Are you jealous?
吃醋
Jealous.
-你吃醋了 -你发什么疯呢
- You're jealous. - You're trippin' girl.
快点 准备武器
Come on. Let's gear up.
散弹枪 不是吧
Shotguns? Really?
受伤的陆战队员
Yeah, wounded Marine.
她手里应该有一把MP5冲锋枪
She's probably armed with a MP5 by now.
还是小心点好
Better safe than sorry.
联邦探员
Federal agents!
Percy
Percy.
这不可能只是抢劫中的枪
No way that's just from the heist shooting.
街对面的房子装有安全监控
House across the street has a security camera,
但摄像头的角度难以确定
but it's a bad angle to I.D. anyone
进出Bellacroix房子的人的身份
going in and out of Bellacroix's place.
所以没人拿着MP5冲锋枪走出来吗
Ooh, so no one walking out with an MP5?
有个拿着小包的女士 就这样
Lady carrying a small bag. That's about it.
这看起来越来越像
It's looking more and more like
那个团伙为了掩盖踪迹干掉了她
the crew took her out to cover their tracks.
找个凶狠的家伙把自己人干掉
Takes a pretty vicious crew to take out one of their own.
我们得查出他们是谁
We need to find out who they are
这样才能尽快找回那些枪
so we can get those guns back, fast.
问题是 他们在掩盖行踪上做得太好了
The problem is, they're so good at covering their tracks,
我们什么都没查到
we got squat.
要是我们能查清楚 一开始是什么让一个光荣的陆战队员
Yeah. If we could just figure out what made a decorated Marine
加入一个抢劫团伙
join a heist crew in the first place.
你确定在她的服役记录中
Are you sure there weren't any red flags
没有任何危险信号吗
in her service record?
没有创伤后应激障碍 没有心理恐慌
No PTSD, no psych alarm.
她的同事中是否有犯罪记录
Any of her known associates with criminal backgrounds?
没有 Bellacroix是新奥尔良本地人
No. Bellacroix's a NOLA native,
路易斯安那州立大学研究生 名列前茅
LSU grad, top of her class.
说了吧 什么都查不到
Like I said, squat.
听我说 我知道监听Hamilton比什么都重要
Look, I know the Hamilton wire is important and everything,
但也许是时候让Pride参与进来了
but think maybe it's time to loop Pride in?
King希望我们能找到线索
King's expecting us to find leads.
继续调查吧
Let's keep digging.
好吧
All right.
嘿 大家好
Hey, guys.
天啊 回到这里看着你们在那边
Oh, man, it's so weird being back here
感觉好奇怪
and seeing you guys there.
这种感觉就像是"我以为自己离开了 他们又把我拉回去..."
It's like, “Just when I thought I was out, they pulled...”
原文：Just when I thought I was out,they pull me back in
是《教父3》里Michael Corleone的台词
It's Michael Corleone, from, uh, from The Godfather 3.
我的屏幕好像... 卡住了
Guys, I think my... my screen froze.
说说被害者的弹道分析
Ballistics on the victim, please.
对 好的
Right, sure.
死者身上的弹道模式表明
Well, the bullet pattern on our dead Marine
13发子弹全部来自于MP5冲锋枪
suggests that all 13 bullets came from an MP5.
要我说 那真是枪林弹雨
Which, if you ask me, that's overkill.
更有理由怀疑 是她的同伙杀了她
Even more reason to suspect her crew took her out.
即使如此 还是有些地方对不上
Still, something doesn't add up.
他们抢劫的时候用的是橡皮子弹
They went out of their way to use rubber bullets
现在却用真的子弹
for the heist, but then use real bullets
去杀自己人吗
to kill one of their own?
或许他们知道 杀警察会被判处死刑
Maybe they knew killing cops guarantees the needle.
但如果他们把其中一把枪变成了杀人凶器
Yeah, but if any of those guns end up as the murder weapon,
他们还是会被判处死刑
they'll get the needle anyway.
我们漏掉了什么
We're missing something.
嗨 那些橡胶子弹有什么发现吗
Hey, did you get anything on those rubber bullets yet?
你们让我验尸完
You wanted me to call
马上给你们打电话
as soon as the autopsy was completed.
哇 嘿 医生
Whoa. Hey, Doc.
简直了 这就跟从前一样
This is so crazy, it's like old times.
你 我 血浆
You, me, plasmas.
我不知道你在你的实验室 Sebastian
I didn't know you were in your lab, Sebastian.
你怎么没来打招呼呢
Why didn't you say something?
我知道当你忙于解剖抽不开身的时候
Well, I know better than to bother you
还是不要打扰你为好
when you're elbow deep in liver.
抱歉打断你们
I hate to interrupt.
验尸结果 对
Autopsy results, right.
好吧 不出所料
Okay, no surprises.
死因是多处枪伤
C.O.D.: multiple gunshot wounds.
子弹击中了每个重要的动脉和器官
The bullets hit every major artery and organ,
击中其中任何一个部位都足以致死
and any one of them would've sufficed.
这显然是一起声明性的谋杀
This was obviously a statement killing.
好让其他成员乖乖听话
One way to keep the rest of the crew in line.
但是 有一个异常
However, there is an anomaly.
在Bellacroix女士被杀之前
Before Ms. Bellacroix was murdered,
有人缝合了她在抢劫时
someone sutured the initial gunshot wound
由铁路警察造成的
inflicted by the railway officer
初始枪伤
during the heist.
甚至取出了子弹
Even removed the bullet.
等等 他们要杀她 为什么还要救她
Wait, why would they try to save her only to kill her?
这根本说不通啊
That doesn't make any sense.
尤其是当你知道 他们还给她
Especially when you factor in that they gave her
用了广谱抗病毒药物 来预防感染
broad-spectrum prophylaxis to fight infection.
移除了子弹 还进行了缝合
Bullet removal, sutures,
抗生素 这必须由
antibiotics-- I mean, this has to
一名医生来完成 是吗
have been done by a doctor, right?
有可能
Maybe.
但她并没有去过医院
But she didn't go to a hospital.
那个提着包的女人
The lady with the bag.
Sebastian 你跟他们说了
Sebastian, did you tell them about
橡胶子弹的事吗
the rubber bullets yet?
没 还没有
No, not yet.
是这样 各地警察都一直希望
So, um, police everywhere have been
越来越多地使用
looking to use more and more
非致命性子弹
nonlethal ammo.
这对枪支制造商来说是个发财的机会
It's been a real boon for gun manufacturers.
幸运的是 每个制造橡胶子弹的公司
Fortunately, each company that makes rubber bullets
都有自己专门的设计 所以
uses its own proprietary design, so,
抢劫团伙使用的子弹
the bullets used by the heist crew
实际上是Bancroft的子弹
are actually Bancroft bullets.
用Bancroft的子弹来偷Bancroft的枪吗
Bancroft bullets used to steal Bancroft guns?
我可能找到了另一个与Bancroft的联系
I might've found another Bancroft connection.
抱歉 医生 我要把屏幕給另一名医生了
Sorry, Doc, I need the screen for another doc.
Emma Miller 一名无国界医生
Emma Miller, a Doctors Without Borders physician,
档案显示 也是Bellacroix的医生
also Bellacroix's doctor of record.
她们一起在新奥尔良长大
They grew up in New Orleans together
同一时间从路易斯安纳州立大学毕业
and graduated LSU at the same time.
这说得通 Bellacroix会找一名医生朋友
Which makes sense Bellacroix would call a doctor friend
来帮她缝合 且不会出卖她
to stitch her up without ratting her out.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我们需要找到Miller医生 看看她怎么说
Yeah, we need to find Dr. Miller and see what she has to say.
与Bancroft的联系是什么
What's the Bancroft connection?
非常大的关系 Miller医生是
A big one. Dr. Miller sits on the board
新奥尔良Bancroft家族基金会的董事会成员
of the Bancroft Family Foundation of New Orleans.
也就是说 她现在可能正在参加慈善舞会
Which means that she could be at that charity shindig right now.
Bancroft的子弹 枪支和朋友
Bancroft bullets, guns and friends.
你们觉得这是内部人搞的事情吗
You guys think this is an inside job?
唯一能让我们搞清楚的方式就是冲进他们的派对了
Only way to find out is for us to crash their little party.
等等
Hold on.
Bancrofts是这里的创始家族
Bancrofts are a founding family here,
有几代人的历史
go back for generations.
我们不能直接冲进去 开始盘问
We can't just show up and start asking questions.
或许我们不能 但是Pride可以
Maybe we can't, but Pride can.
♪ 你开着你的悍马 ♪
♪ You pull up in your Hummer ♪
♪ 停在了我的沃蓝达旁边 ♪
♪ And you park next to my Volt ♪
♪ 你穿着阿玛尼三件套 ♪
♪ Wearing Armani three-piece ♪
♪ 我穿着满是洞的李维斯 ♪
♪ I wear Levi's full of holes ♪
♪ 我或许会沿着左边走 ♪
♪ I might walk along the left side ♪
♪ 而你沿着右边走 ♪
♪ And you walk along the right ♪
♪ 我们都要去相同的地方 ♪
♪ We're both trying to reach the same place ♪
♪ 我们或许不能按时到达 ♪
♪ We might not get there on time ♪
♪ 但你知道最妙的是什么吗 ♪
♪ But you know what's best... ♪
歌名《Halfway There》
一个小派对
Some little party.
他们居然请来了Sheryl Crow 不是吧
They landed Sheryl Crow, really?
二十世纪90年代以来最受欢迎的摇滚乐女歌手之一
这是为了行善
Well, it is for a good cause.
♪ 接下来的我们都知道 是的 ♪
♪ We all know the rest, yeah ♪
♪ 宝贝 如果你够胆 ♪
♪ Baby, if you dare ♪
♪ 如果你真的在意 ♪
♪ If you really care ♪
♪ 宝贝 如果你够胆 ♪
♪ Baby, if you dare ♪
♪ 你要不要在半路和我相遇 ♪
♪ Won't you meet me halfway there... ♪
或许我们应该走慢点
Maybe we should walk a little slower, you know?
这样就能多看会儿表演了
So we can catch the show.
我们不是来这儿要签名的
We're not here for autographs.
那么多枪遗落街头 这些人居然还能开派对
These people have guns out on the street and they're partying.
十分感谢你们
Thank you for giving so generously
对2017年Bancroft基金人道主义援助的慷慨支持
to the Bancroft Foundation Humanitarian Aid 2017.
Justus Bancroft吗
Justus Bancroft?
特别探员Dwayne Pride
Special Agent Dwayne Pride.
聊一下
A moment?
请容我失陪
Will you excuse me, please?
♪ 我喜欢那阳光 ♪
♪ I like the sunshine... ♪
如果是要谈那些丢失的枪
Now, look, if this about those stolen guns,
现在不是时候
now is not the best time.
有人被你的枪所杀 Bancroft先生
Someone was killed with one of your guns, Mr. Bancroft.
如果我们不尽快找出是谁偷了那些枪
And if we don't find out who stole them real soon,
或许会有更多人丧命
more will likely die.
尽管如此 这里有很多非常重要的人物
Well, still, there are a lot of very important people here.
这是为了你好
Well, good for you.
你见过Emma Miller医生吗
Have you seen Dr. Emma Miller?
当然 她帮助我们建立基金会
Well, sure, of course. She helped set up.
她和这件事有什么关系
What's she got to do with this?
我们还不确定 所以我们想要和她谈谈
Yeah, we're not sure. That's why we want to talk to her.
我们会低调进行的
We'll be discreet.
分组搜查
Split up, search the grounds.
明白
You got it.
爸爸 出什么事了
Daddy, what's going on?
不用担心 没什么
Oh, nothing to worry about,
Nadine 亲爱的 他们只是在找Emma
Nadine, honey, they're just looking for Emma.
你看见过她吗
Have you seen her?
见过 她就在附近 但是你们不能待会再找她吗
Yeah, she's here somewhere, but can't you do this later?
恐怕不行
Afraid not.
你对Miller医生了解多少
How well do you know Dr. Miller?
她就像是我的姐姐
She's like a sister to me.
我们是永远的朋友
We've been friends for forever.
Pride 我们有麻烦了
Pride, we got a problem.
我们在喷泉后面
We're behind the fountains.
过来看看
Come take a look at this.
♪ 宝贝 我不喜欢等待 ♪
♪ Baby, I don't like to wait... ♪
怎么了 Chris
What is it, Chris?
Caterer回来这里拿香槟
Caterer came back here to get more champagne.
Emma Miller
Emma Miller.
被处决 跟Bellacroix一样
Executed, just like Bellacroix.
看上去是两三个小时前发生的
Looks like it happened a couple hours ago.
甚至可能在派对开始前
Maybe even before the party started.
我们刚从Miller医生的家里回来
Well, we just got back from Dr. Miller's house.
找到了防弹衣 帽子和夜视镜
Found body armor, a balaclava and night vision goggles.
所以 除非她是喜欢深夜在敌人的火力下进行手术
So, unless she liked performing surgery in the dark
不然她就是抢劫团伙的一员
and under enemy fire, I'd say she was part of the heist crew.
团伙中有两个女人吗 这不太正常啊
Two women on the crew? That's unusual.
但如果这是真的 那团伙成员想掩盖行踪
Yeah, but if it's true, it doesn't make sense
就解释不通了
that the crew's trying to cover their tracks now.
一定是有其他人在针对她们
It's got to be somebody else targeting them.
比如 敌对团伙吗
Like what, a rival crew?
想为他们自己搞到那些枪 也是有可能
Trying to get the guns for themselves, possibly.
可能有个黑市买手出卖了她们
Could be a black market buyer double-crossing them.
你在Miller家里找到橡胶子弹了吗
You find any rubber bullets at Miller's house?
找到了 有几个盒子 都是Bancroft产的
Yeah, several boxes, actually. All of them made by Bancroft.
Bancroft的名字一直在不停出现 不是吗
Bancroft's name just keeps popping up, doesn't it?
出现的地方比你想的要多
Popping up in more places than you think.
你们来听听这个 但得快点
You need to hear this, but hurry.
你需要命令NCIS
You need to get NCIS
别再找我麻烦 知道吗
off my back, you understand?
我不能让他们调查那些失踪的枪支
I can't have them investigating those missing guns,
-现在不行 -什么意思
- not now. - What does that mean?
难道你知道它们的去向
You know where they are?
Hamilton市长
Mayor Hamilton?
Hamilton在电话里
Hamilton was on the phone just starting
正想讨论清水市 Bancroft就闯进来了
to talk about Clearwater when Bancroft bulled his way in.
-嘘 -但是我和NCIS之间
- Shh. - But I got enough
麻烦已经够多了
of my own problems with NCIS.
对此我也无能为力
There's nothing I can do.
你可以利用你的关系
You can use your connections.
越过他们
Go over their heads.
说你可以自己把枪找回来 变成英雄
Say you'll get the guns back on your own. Be a hero.
那我又怎样恰好找回了那些枪呢
Yeah, and how am I supposed to get those guns back exactly?
这事交给我
You leave that to me.
和清水市没什么关系
Wasn't anything to do with Clearwater,
但我认为不管怎样都应该录下来
but I thought I should record it anyway.
难以相信Bancroft偷了他自己的枪
Can't believe Bancroft stole his own guns.
问题是 为什么呢
Yeah, question is: why?
这么一家金融巨头
Company's doing great financially,
不缺这点儿保险赔偿
doesn't need the insurance payoff.
有什么关系 反正我们也不能用刚刚听到的消息
Doesn't matter, we can't use what we just heard anyway.
窃听范围
Scope of the wiretap
仅限于Hamilton和清水市
is only for Hamilton and Clearwater.
我们不能就这样忽视它
Well, we can't just ignore it.
所有人都把他牵扯进来了
Man all but incriminated himself.
为什么你不直接逮捕Bancroft 给他施压
Why don't you just bring Bancroft in, scare him?
之后再让律师辩论
And let the lawyers argue
这是否被允许
whether it was admissible or not later.
因为那样Bancroft就会发现录音的事情
Because then Bancroft would find out about the tap,
意味着Hamilton也会知道
which means so would Hamilton.
这会毁掉你唯一扳倒他的机会
And then it would blow your one chance to bring him down.
但是另一方面 因为这批枪
Yeah, on the other hand, two people are already dead
已经死了两个人
'cause of those guns.
在我们将他们捉拿归案前 还有多少人会因此而死
How many more are gonna die before we get them back?
所以你打算怎么办
So what are you gonna do?
你做了一个错误的决定
You're making a mistake.
风险太大了 Pride 只是说说
It's a big risk, Pride. Just saying.
希望我们不会因此失去扳倒Hamilton的机会
Hope we don't lose Hamilton over it.
我也是
Me, too.
不得不说 我有一点吃惊
Got to say, I'm a little surprised.
凭你的本事
Man of your means--
还以为 你现在会要求一个律师
would've thought you'd have asked for a lawyer by now.
我是无辜的 我不需要律师
I'm innocent. I don't need a lawyer.
无辜的人不会让自己犯罪的
Well, innocent men don't tend to incriminate themselves,
Bancroft先生
Mr. Bancroft.
如果我已经有了逮捕令 你会怎么想
How else do you think I would've gotten an arrest warrant?
我不知道 请你直说
I don't know, you tell me.
Patton
Patton?
好
Yeah.
不好意思 Bancroft
I'm sorry, Bancroft,
但是我和NCIS之间的麻烦已经够多了
but I got enough of my own problems with NCIS.
对此我也无能为力
There's nothing I can do.
你可以利用你的关系
You can use your connections,
越过他们
go over their heads.
说你可以自己把枪找回来 变成英雄
Say you'll get the guns back on your own. Be a hero.
那我又该怎样恰好找回了那些枪呢
Yeah, and how am I supposed to get those guns back exactly?
这事交给我
You leave that to me.
我听着不像是无辜的啊
Doesn't sound so innocent to me.
这是断章取义
That is taken out of context.
另外 你是怎么得到这个的
Besides, how'd you get that?
你窃听我吗 理由是什么
You put a tap on me? On what grounds?
不是窃听你 而是市长
Tap wasn't on you. It was on the mayor.
你只是求错了人
You just got help from the wrong person,
然后被逮到了
got caught.
我不在乎你为什么要偷自己的枪
I don't give a damn why you stole your own guns.
我只想在更多的人被杀害前 找回这批枪
I just want to get 'em back before anybody else gets killed.
我没有偷
I didn't steal them.
那你为什么知道这批枪在哪儿
Then why do you know where the guns are?
为什么你跟Hamilton说你可以把枪拿回来
How come you told Hamilton you can get 'em back?
除非你开始坦白 地检署将会指控你
Unless you start talking, U.S. attorney's gonna charge you
作为共犯 重度谋杀罪
as a coconspirator, felony murder.
你不想以后的人生都在监狱度过吧
You don't want to spend the rest of your life in prison,
坦白 快点
talk... fast.
我不能
I can't.
不好意思 Pride 但是Izzo来了
Sorry, Pride, but Izzo's here.
她坚持要跟你谈话
She insists on talking to you.
你知道当初我单单为了安装窃听设备
Do you realize how many hoops I had to jump through
就要突破多少障碍吗
just to get that wiretap granted in the first place?
我知道 Karen 但是我必须
I know, Karen, but I had...
没有但是 Dwayne
No buts, Dwayne.
你用窃听Hamilton得到的证据逮捕了Bancroft
You based the arrest of Bancroft on Hamilton's wiretap.
一个优秀的被告辩护律师不会这么容易善罢甘休的
A good defense attorney will get that kicked easily.
Bancroft犯了罪
Well, Bancroft incriminated himself.
那我应该怎么办
What was I supposed to do?
你就应该忽视掉
You were supposed to ignore
你所听到的 那就是该做的
what you heard, that's what.
太多的枪消失了 我需要做出选择
Too many guns are missing. I had to make a choice.
这是一个可能会让你失去
A choice that's probably gonna cost you
扳倒Hamilton的机会的选择
any chance of bringing down Hamilton.
他会发现的 如果他现在还没有的话
He's gonna find out, if he hasn't already.
我稍后会考虑这个问题的
I'll worry about that later.
不 你现在就应该考虑
No, you need to worry about that now.
Dwayne 如果Hamilton市长真的像你说的那么不堪
Dwayne, if Mayor Hamilton is as dirty as you say he is,
他会报复你的
he's going to retaliate.
你知道他会
You know he will.
我不会让更多的人被杀害
I wasn't gonna let more people get killed.
你应该打电话给我
You should've called me!
我没有时间 我必须行动
I didn't have time, I had to act.
我警告过你
I warned you.
我警告过你用监听的方式
I warned you about the risk
调查Hamilton这种大人物
of going after a powerful man like Hamilton,
风险有多高
about blowing the wire.
你完全没意识到你在做什么
You have no idea what you've done.
她看起来不怎么高兴
Well, she doesn't seem happy.
她是不高兴
She's not.
但还是回到正题吧
But let's stay on point.
Bancroft不肯开口 我想我知道原因
Bancroft's not talking, and I think I know why.
我不知道他是怎么跟被偷的枪支牵扯上的
I don't know how he's involved with the stolen guns,
但是我丝毫不怀疑
but there's no question in my mind
他知道这批枪在哪儿
that he knows where they are.
-但他还是不会告诉你 -不会
- But he still wouldn't tell you? - Nope.
我认为他在保护某个人
And I think it's because he's protecting somebody,
某个他宁愿为其蹲监狱的人
somebody he's willing to go to jail for.
他的女儿
His daughter.
Nadine怎么会
How can Nadine
牵扯进这种事
possibly be involved in this?
她牵扯的程度可能比你想象的要深
Well, she may be more involved than you think.
我用先进的链接和社交网络分析
I just ran case and victim profiles
运行了案例和受害者资料
through advanced link and social network analysis;
猜猜谁的名字出现在得分榜上
guess whose name lit up the scoreboard.
Nadine Bancroft
Nadine Bancroft.
她也涉及到数个不同层面的案件
She connects to the case on several levels, too:
地域 社会经济 年龄 学校 社交媒体
geographic, socioeconomic, age, schools, social media.
在另外三个朋友的婚礼上
I mean, all were bridesmaids
她都是伴娘
at three other friends' weddings.
无国界医生 陆战队员
Doctors Without Borders, Marines,
Nadine加入了和平队
Nadine joined the Peace Corps.
这些人并不仅仅是一群富豪
I mean, these are hardly just a bunch of rich debutantes.
可以解释为什么没有人能抓住这个团队
Could explain why nobody's been able to catch the crew.
没有人会怀疑他们 而且
Nobody would ever suspect them, plus...
Nadine知道怎样窃取枪支
Nadine would know exactly how to steal the guns
而不被抓住
without getting caught.
你是很认真地在说
Are you seriously suggesting that
Nadine Bancroft是抢劫团伙的一员吗
Nadine Bancroft is part of the heist crew?
她从自己家偷枪支 为什么呢
That she stole the guns from her own family? Why?
不知道 但是如果他父亲发现她做的事情
Don't know, but if her father found out what she was doing,
他在努力保护她 这是说得通的
makes sense he's trying to protect her.
这也是为什么他跟Hamilton说会帮忙找回枪支
And that's why he told Hamilton he'd get him back the guns.
所以 这位富家女是在博人眼球吗
So, what, Silver Spoon here is vying for attention?
在反对他们多么有钱 还是什么
Rebelling against how rich they are or something?
不 他们这样做一定有别的原因
Nah, there's got to be another reason why they're doing this.
不管什么理由 这是一大批枪
Yeah, it's a lot of guns, whatever the reason.
问题是 除非我们找出原因 否则就不会知道
Problem is, we're never gonna figure out who's killing off
是谁在杀害抢劫团伙
the heist crew unless we figure out why.
意思是 他们接下来可能会杀Nadine
Which means, they could be after Nadine next.
通知警方
Alert NOPD.
让他们去Bancroft家
Get 'em out to the Bancrofts'.
出发
Let's go.
我们到了现场 Christopher 准备
We're on scene, Christopher. Stand by.
收到 发现Nadine了吗
Copy that. Any sign of Nadine?
没 暂时没有
No, not yet.
有人开枪
Shots fired!
我认为他们已经抓到了Nadine
I think they've got Nadine!
我们还在追
We're in pursuit!
他们正朝你方向逃去
They're coming your way!
围住他们
Box 'em in!
我们马上就到
We're almost there.
他们来了 我们围到他们了 Pride
Here they come! We got 'em, Pride!
趴下 Nadine
Drop, Nadine!
你安全了
You're okay.
你安全了 你安全了
You're okay. You're okay.
我不想催你 Loretta 但
Hate to rush you, Loretta, but...
请告诉我 你能确认他们的身份
please tell me you can help us identify...
他们是博科圣地的人
They're Boko Haram.
尼日利亚极端组织
至少这两个人隶属于
At least, that's the particular terrorist group
这个恐怖组织
these two gunmen belonged to.
博科圣地出现在新奥尔良
Boko Haram in New Orleans?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
很不幸 我确定
Unfortunately, I am.
注意那条从额头到鼻子的伤疤
Notice the scarring from forehead to nose,
脸上还有两条笔直的线
the two rectilinear lines down the cheeks.
部落伤疤
Tribal scars.
许多非洲少数民族使用不同的面部标识
Many African ethnic groups use distinctive facial markings--
约鲁巴人 伊博人 豪撒人 但这两位是卡努里人
Yoruba, Igbo, Hausa-- but these men are Kanuri.
他们被博科圣地重金招募
Heavily recruited by Boko Haram.
我一直都不敢相信 直到
I couldn't believe it myself until
在他脚踝上看到了这个瘢痕纹身
I saw the keloid tattoo on their ankles.
BH
“BH.”
我在非洲做了很长时间的
You know how much time I've spent
志愿者 Dwayne
volunteering in Africa, Dwayne.
我亲眼见过
I've witnessed firsthand
这些畜生在无辜的女人和孩子身上
the horrors these animals perpetrate
干的坏事
on innocent women and children.
我知道 Loretta
I know, Loretta.
我们会尽全力阻止他们
We're gonna do everything we can to stop them.
问题是
Yeah, the question is:
他们在这里干什么
what are they doing here?
为什么要杀抢劫团伙呢
And why are they killing the heist crew?
他们肯定想要那些枪
They must want the guns.
但是 他们一开始是怎么知道
But still, how'd they know Nadine and her crew
Nadine和她的人想要偷走枪呢
were gonna steal the guns in the first place?
不知道
I don't know.
也许Nadine能告诉我们
Maybe Nadine could tell us.
告诉其他人 我们马上回去
Let the rest of the team know we're heading back.
让Gregorio
Have Gregorio
通报国土安全部和FBI
alert DHS and FBI.
我怀疑 这只是袭击小队中的两名成员而已
Doubt these are the only two members of the hit squad,
我们需要其他机构帮忙 追捕其他人
which means we could use a lot of help finding the others.
这就去
On it.
他们肯定要活捉Nadine 而不是杀害她
Must've taken Nadine instead of killing her
希望她能告诉他们枪在哪儿
in hopes that she would tell 'em where the guns were hidden.
肯定要对她严刑逼供
No doubt by torturing her.
你说什么
What do you mean?
那位海军陆战队员
From the Marine.
韧带撕裂 死前挫伤
Torn ligaments, antemortem bruising.
初步检查的时候没有发现
I didn't see it in the prelim,
但是这个可怜的女人在死前
but the poor woman was clearly tortured
肯定被严刑逼供了
before she was executed.
他们可能从她这儿获取了所有想要的情报
They would've gotten everything they wanted from her.
Dwayne
Dwayne,
一定要抓住这些混蛋
you've got to get these bastards.
但要小心
But be careful.
你们救了我 我很感激
You saved my life, and I'm grateful.
但我不能告诉你们枪在哪里
But I can't tell you where the guns are.
好吧 我不明白
Okay, I don't understand.
你偷了你父亲的枪
You stole your father's guns.
两个伙伴被杀了
Two of your friends were killed,
你差点儿被杀
you were nearly killed,
为什么还不配合我们
and you won't cooperate with us?
你以为你是谁
Who do you think you are?
这不重要 你不会相信我
Doesn't matter, you won't believe me.
试试看
Try me.
Emma和我几年前去过苏丹的城市Jo
Emma and I visited Jo in Sudan a couple of years ago.
我们都很震惊
We were shocked.
那儿和这儿有天壤之别
It couldn't have been more different than here--
战乱 饥荒
war-torn, famine.
那儿是人道主义灾难
Place is a humanitarian disaster.
我们自愿在[苏丹首都]喀土穆帮助村民
We volunteered to help villagers set up
建立起一座女子学校
a girls' school in Khartoum,
但是博科圣地发动了袭击
but then Boko Haram attacked.
我们逃到大使馆
We were whisked
寻求庇护 但是
into the embassy for safety, but...
我们通过大门看到不断发生的袭击
we watched the attack keep happening through the gates.
但是没人想去阻止
And nobody tried to stop it.
女人被强暴
Women being raped,
孩子被射杀
children being shot.
我们却无能为力
And there was nothing we could do.
你不可能忘记这些事
You don't ever unsee something like that.
枪是给村民的
Guns are for the villagers.
用来保护自己
To protect themselves.
因为没有人会保护他们
'Cause nobody else will.
但博科圣地一定是发现了
But Boko Haram must've found out
我们做的事
what we've been doing,
所以他们来到这里 要阻止我们
so they came here to try and stop us.
这是个崇高的动机
It's a noble cause,
但这是完全违法的
but it's-it's completely illegal.
偷枪
Stealing guns,
走私到海外
smuggling them out of the country...
违反了15条联邦法律 你是知道的
breaks 15 federal laws, you know that.
你真的愿意冒着生命危险这么做 对吗
You're really willing to risk your life for this, aren't you?
是的
Yes, I am.
如果你们不让我走
If you don't let me go,
不把枪给村民
get the villagers those guns...
博科圣地会一直袭击他们
...Boko Haram will keep attacking them
直到他们全死光
until they're all dead.
你真的能接受吗
Can you really live with that?
我们必须想办法帮她
We have to find a way to help her.
没办法帮她 Sonja
Well, there's no way to help her, Sonja.
我们不能放她走
We can't let her go.
但要是Nadine说的是真的呢
But what if Nadine's right?
我们不能眼睁睁看着那些人死去
We can't just let those people die.
这事儿发生在大半个地球外
It's halfway around the world.
这样的人到处都有
There's people like that everywhere,
我们帮不了所有人
we can't help 'em all.
但我们现在了解了这些人的情况
Yeah, but we know about these people
也能帮助他们
and can do something about it.
帮助Nadine就意味着犯法
Helping Nadine means breaking the law.
那又怎样 我们之前为了做正确的事
So? We've risked breaking the law before
也冒险行走在法律边缘
to do the right thing.
但这次不同 情况不一样
Not like this. This is different.
怎么会 有什么不同
How? How is this different?
如果你非要问
If you have to ask,
那说明你没有在理智思考
you're not thinking straight.
现在深呼吸
Now take a breath.
看来
Seems like
我们现在进退两难
we're danged if we do and danged if we don't.
如果我们不做点什么
I mean, if we don't do something,
恐怖分子肯定会抢走枪
the terrorists are gonna get their hands on them guns anyway.
还可能用它们来对付那些
Yeah, and probably use them against the very people
Nadine想要救的人
Nadine's trying to save.
Nadine也知道这个情况
Nadine knows we know that, too,
可能因此希望我们放了她
probably hoping we'll let her go because of it.
真是进退维谷
It's a catch-22.
好了
All right,
我们放她走
we'll let her go.
但要跟着她 让她带我们找到枪
But only to follow her so she leads us to the guns.
等等 你是说我们要给她下套吗
Wait, you mean we're gonna trick her?
不是下套 是要救她
No, not trying to trick her, trying to save her life
同时 不让博科圣地得到那些枪
and keep Boko Haram from getting those guns.
我们只能帮她到这儿了
And that's gonna have to be enough for you.
明白了吗
Clear?
Nadine正向东走
Nadine's still heading east towards
沿着星条大道
Stars and Stripes Boulevard,
时速超过限速15英里
going about 15 miles over the speed limit,
也许你想把这条也加入指控
in case you want to add that to the charges.
她是去机场吗
Think she's heading to the airport?
希望不是
I hope not,
因为所有光学测距器的单元信号
'cause all the RF and cell signals
都可能破坏你放在她口袋里的追踪器
might screw up the geotracker you put in her coat.
全靠你了 Patton
Counting on you, Patton.
我们得离她足够近才能保护她
We got to stay close enough to protect her
以防恐怖分子袭击她
in case the terrorists attack,
但不能太近 防止她发现我们
but not so close that she spots us.
我想知道他们为什么还没袭击她
I wonder why they haven't attacked her yet.
也许他们已经找到枪了
Maybe they already found the guns,
要是这样的话 他们就不需要跟着她了
and if so, they don't need to follow her.
除非他们一开始就不是冲着枪而来
Except they didn't come for the guns first,
而是冲着Nadine来的
they came for Nadine.
不要担心 我们会保护她的
Don't worry, we're not gonna let anything happen to her.
记住 一旦她带我们找到枪
Just remember, as soon as she leads us to the guns,
我们就要逮捕Nadine
we got to get Nadine,
拿到枪 然后离开
get the guns, and then get out of there.
特别是当他们已经找到了枪的情况
Especially if they already found them.
他们可能就在那儿等她
They could be lying in wait for her.
她从Crofton下去了
She's getting off on Crofton.
可能是去出租的飞机棚
She might be headed to the charter hangars.
该死 她的信号中断了
Damn it, her signal's breaking up.
我们得拉近距离
We got to close the gap.
我不明白这事 Christopher
I don't know about this, Christopher.
我还是不敢相信 我们要逮捕她
I still can't believe we're gonna arrest her.
King做了决定 我们做好自己的工作就行了
King made the call. Let's just do our jobs.
这个集装箱应该已经卸货了
The storage pods were supposed to be unloaded
并且已经在飞机上了 我没法等那么久
and on the plane by now. I can't wait that long.
对不起 Nadine 但我们得推迟
I'm sorry, Nadine, but we got delayed
到达机场
getting to the airport.
等等 有些不对劲
Wait. Something's happened.
枪在哪儿
Where are the guns?
你什么意思 什么枪在哪儿
What do you mean, where are the guns?
Nadine 怎么了
Nadine, what's wrong?
一切都还好吗
Is everything okay?
Nadine Nadine
Nadine? Nadine!
嘿
Hey!
你在干什么
What are you doing...
Nadine 停下
Nadine, stop!
你跟踪我
You followed me.
是的 而且又一次救了你的命
Yeah, and saved your life again.
-跑去候机楼 -我得跑的更远一些
- Run to the terminal. - I'm gonna run farther than that.
博科圣地会为了这事儿报复村民的
Boko Haram's gonna retaliate against the villagers for this.
如果我没法把枪给他们 至少让我警示他们
If I can't get them guns, at least let me warn them,
让他们离开
move them.
我有办法
I have the means.
如果你允许 我可以很快离开这个国家
I can easily leave the country if you let me.
对不起 Nadine 我不能
No, I'm sorry, Nadine, I can't.
拜托了
Please.
Percy 你没事吧
Percy, you good?
Nadine怎么样了
How's Nadine?
她去哪儿了
Where is she?
她 她跑了
Sh-She got away.
陪着他
Stay with him.
我想知道今天外面发生了些什么
I want to know what happened out there today.
我已经告诉你我知道的了 Pride
I told you what I know, Pride.
你告诉了我 你想让我知道的
You told me what you want me to know.
Nadine不可能在你手下跑了
No way Nadine got away from you.
见鬼了 Sonja
Damn it, Sonja,
Brody走后 我努力重建这支队伍
I worked too hard to rebuild this team after Brody left.
比以前更强大了
Stronger than ever.
你怎么可以冒险把这一切都毁了呢
How could you be so willing to risk throwing it all away?
这个队伍对你的意义 不比别人少吧
This team means as much, if not more, to you than to anybody.
这知道
I know that.
那你为什么不告诉我到底发生了什么
Then why the hell won't you tell me what happened?
有什么区别呢
What difference does it make?
我们抓到了恐怖分子 对吗
We got the terrorists, didn't we?
还有枪支
And the guns.
Nadine不是坏人
Nadine is not the bad guy.
那怎么那么多执法部门
Then how come half of law enforcement's
仍然在外面找她
still out there looking for her?
如果我告诉你了 Pride 任何这间办公室之外的人
If I told you, Pride, and anybody outside of this office
发现了真相
found out,
你也会有麻烦的
you would get in trouble, too.
我不能让这一切发生
I can't let that happen.
我已经陷入麻烦了
I'm already in trouble.
为了这事我牺牲了抓捕Hamilton的机会
I sacrificed Hamilton for this.
天知道他会怎么报复
God only knows how he's gonna retaliate.
这很严重 Sonja
This is serious, Sonja.
不仅仅是法律问题
Not just legally.
你不能报喜不报忧
You cannot cherry-pick which orders to follow--
至少在我眼皮底下不行
not on my watch.
这不是一支队伍应该有的
That is not what a team is.
我也不会支持你
And I won't stand for it.
我们之前就已经谈过了
And we've had this conversation before.
Nadine到底怎么了
What happened to Nadine?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能说
I can't.
就这样吧
That'll be all.
嘿
Hey.
你在等我吗
You waited for me?
我有些担心
Well, I was a little worried.
一切都好吗
Everything all right?
我不知道
I don't know.
Pride很生气
Pride is pretty pissed.
我不能怪他
Can't say I blame him.
我 但我不知道他会做什么
And I... I don't know what he's gonna do yet.
什么意思 做什么
What does that mean? Do what?
我不知道他会不会向总部举报我
I don't know if he's gonna report me to HQ.
King不会这么做的
King's not gonna do that.
他知道这样你就完了
He knows you'll be done for.
是啊 可我说了 他非常生气
Yeah, like I said, he's pretty pissed.
你告诉他究竟发生了什么吗
Well, did you tell him what really happened?
什么 你也想知道么
What, you're trying to find out, too?
不相信我吗
Don't you trust me?
你有吃醋吗
Were you jealous?
在咖啡店的男人
Guy in the coffee shop.
这有什么联系呢
Now, what does that got to do with...
啊 你不能指望我相信你
Ah, you can't expect me to trust you
如果你不相信我 对吗
if you don't trust me, right?
好吧 老实说 我不知道我什么感觉
Well, honestly, I don't know what I felt.
我
I...
可能有一点点的吃醋吧
Maybe I could have been a little jealous.
那也许我可能让Nadine跑了
And maybe I could have let Nadine go.
听着 我不需要你给我讲道理 Christopher
Hey, look, I don't need a lecture from you, Christopher,
我也不想让这事影响到你
and I don't want this to bite you in the ass later,
所以拜托了
so please,
别问我任何问题了好吗
don't ask me any more questions, okay?
好的
Okay.
走吧 我们离开这儿
Come on, let's get out of here.
Percy
Percy.
刚和助理检察官Lzzo通了电话
Just got off the phone with Assistant U.S. Attorney Izzo.
法官想让我们现在就去市中心
Judge wants us both downtown now.
证据明显
The evidence clearly contradicts
和Percy探员在法庭上的证词相违背
Agent Percy's statement to the court.
你撒谎了
You lied.
没有 是这样
No. See...
当时队伍正处在枪战之中 我...
the team was in the middle of a firefight. I...
你在你宣誓过的证词中
You said in your sworn statement,
是这么说的"Nadine Bancroft逃跑了"
and I quote, “Nadine Bancroft got away.”
明显地 你本可以在那个时候逮捕她
Clearly, you could have arrested her right then and there.
在你回到队伍之前 把她逮捕
Cuffed her before you went back in.
我担心我的队伍
I was worried about my team.
我做了主观决定
I made a judgment call.
你让一个重罪犯逃跑了
You let a felon escape.
好的 等等
Okay, hold on.
单纯出于好奇
Just out of curiosity...
是什么让你去看监控的
what made you think to look for surveillance?
这不是重点
That's not the point.
这更像是报复而不是追求正义
It is if this is more about retribution than justice.
你是在宽恕你探员的行为吗 Pride探员
Are you condoning your agent's behavior, Agent Pride?
我不宽恕以莫须有罪名进行政治迫害
I'm not condoning a witch hunt, if that's what you're asking.
你俩到底在说什么
What the hell are you two talking about?
尊敬的法官大人 Pride探员和Hamilton市长
Your Honor, Agent Pride and Mayor Hamilton
相处的不是很愉快
don't exactly get along.
那又和这事有什么关系
And what does that have to do with this?
因为市长听说发生的事情之后
Because when the mayor heard about what happened,
他叫了督察长开始新的调查
he asked the inspector general to open an investigation.
报复我调查他的事儿
Retribution for my investigating him.
-纯属推测 -说的跟真的一样
- Conjecture. - Like hell it is!
够了
Enough.
你们俩可以晚些继续吵
You two can argue about this later.
但这没有改变事实
But it doesn't change the facts.
你有大麻烦了 年轻的女士
You're in serious trouble, young lady.
因为在我眼里
Because as far as I'm concerned,
你没有说实话
you're not telling me the truth.
你有最后一次机会
You have one last chance.
我想知道你为什么没有逮捕 Nadine Bancroft
I want to know why you didn't arrest Nadine Bancroft,
我想知道她在哪儿
and I want to know where she is,
否则我要判你伪证罪
or I'm gonna charge you with perjury
以及轻视法庭
and hold you in contempt.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
Karen Karen 等等 等等
Karen, Karen, come on, come on.
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
别怪我 Dwayne
Don't blame me, Dwayne.
你探员自找的
Your agent brought this on herself.
我只是做本职工作
I'm just doing my job.
是啊 更像是执行Hamilton的命令
Yeah, more like doing Hamilton's bidding.
没想到你也是和市长同一阵营的
Didn't realize that you were in the mayor's pocket, too.
你知道这不是真的
You know that's not true.
是吗
Do I?
底线是
Bottom line:
你的探员搞砸了 Hamilton反扑了
your agent screwed up, and Hamilton pounced.
我警告过你 如果他发现窃听一事的后果
I warned you what would happen if he found out about the wire.
没什么我能做的
There's nothing I could do.
这不是真的
That's not true.
你让他开了场 现在你必须接受事实
You gave him the opening, now you have to live with it.
刚发生了什么 King
What just happened, King?
Percy呢
Where's Percy?
他们要带她去监狱
They're taking her to jail.